[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Ma'am, thank you.
Not at all.
Why isn't the pretty girl here?
What do you want?
Be careful. Her boyfriend is right next to you.
That way.
Hey, who exactly are you guys? What do you want from me?
What do you know about Yuan Tao?
If Yuan Tao doesn't fall,
my business will stall.
A lot of investors are ditching stocks for that crypto coin.
It's all their fault.
Do you know Yuan Tao has a separate company called Tolita?
-Are they related? -Yes.
Tolita is in your line of work.
They run scams.
No wonder they could afford a prime location from day one.
We need your help to scam Tolita.
You'll get a big cut when it's done.
So you guys want to scam a peer.
Targeting a peer is tough.
I want a deposit.
Send it to me within three days.
Money is not an issue.
Out with the old, in with the new.
It's a privilege for an old guy like me to learn from the next generation.
Don't cheat us.
…an exciting investment opportunity with Dolly Bit.
We all know Bitcoin has grown tremendously since its launch in 2009.
In 2024, it rose above $100,000 for the first time…
THE FIXERS
DIAMOND ICE
A friend who sources seafood
gave me some kind of investment link.
It seemed okay when I looked it up online.
She taught classes on crypto to members.
She claimed to be teaching us how to fish.
She invited us into the group and gave us some treats.
Once you got those free coins,
you could invest using their app.
They drove up the price so you thought you were making a profit.
-Four Dots. -Pung.
Later, I discovered she didn't teach us how to fish or give us any fish.
She only gave us bait. I was the fish.
-Six Dots. -Pung again.
-Are you even listening? -Yeah. Who says I'm not?
Then I found out the app was completely fake.
The bullish chart was all a lie.
When I told her I wanted to sell, guess what she said?
"Ms. Wu, I'm sorry, our system is down."
Or she would say, "Your account is frozen."
Sounds like every crypto scam company uses pretty much the same tactics.
-Nine Characters. -I won.
Thanks, buddy.
Actually, it's not just me.
Several of my customers were also scammed.
-That's not right. -What?
It's not news that you're bad at mah-jongg.
He was clearly waiting for either 1, 4, and 7, or 3, 6, and 9.
You fed him the win with a 1.
-What's wrong? -Exactly.
What I meant was
if the app was fake,
someone would have noticed.
I was listening, okay?
You're great at keeping track of the tiles.
At the time, everyone had their eyes on making money.
Who would have thought that it was fake?
Just like you.
You were so eager to toss the 9. So what happened to your money?
All gone.
Why did you ask about all this?
It's just…
Our company is conducting anti-fraud training for employees.
That's so nice.
Perfect for you.
Gosh, don't embarrass me in front of your boss.
Don't be embarrassed. You really need it.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to know how your search for Gerald is going.
Oh, I see.
I thought I was in trouble.
Well, so, we've discovered
that Yuan Tao cofounder, Zoe, was connected to Gerald.
He disappeared right around the time Zoe died.
We also learned that Zoe and her partner, William, had a falling-out.
We are trying to approach William.
How will you do that?
William set up a company called Tolita, which runs scams.
We want to use this company to find evidence of his fraudulent activities
and force him to tell us more about Zoe.
Well, um, I heard from Fixer Gold
that Gerald is crucial to Ching He's survival.
Is that true?
Two types of people are especially dangerous.
Those who possess crucial evidence.
And those who know too much.
Pretend I didn't ask.
I want to live a little longer.
I'm going now.
Pretend I never asked.
ZOE
Hey, Ben.
Did you open this stall first or the arcade?
My dad left me this stall.
I took over right after he passed away.
I bought the arcade after I retired.
What did you do before that?
Didn't Mina tell you that I used to be a fixer too?
You were a fixer too? She didn't say.
We've barely talked to each other.
Don't you think she's difficult?
Don't you think talking behind people's backs
is really rude?
Your usual?
What's her usual?
Tien-bu-la. No radishes or pork meatballs.
What's the point if you don't want those two?
If she doesn't want them, give them to me.
Hey, there you are. Want some?
Oh, sure.
-What would you like to eat? -Tien-bu-la.
No blood pudding or deep-fried tofu.
Goddamn.
Are difficult people all picky eaters?
Young people these days, jeez.
They don't eat this or that. Such a pain in the butt.
Just put both in one bowl.
-In one bowl? -Yes, just do as I say.
Here, only one bowl left.
You two will have to make do and share.
Share it.
The app already shows a 15% profit.
You move fast. Have you already invested in it?
I bought it.
Ben, contact a crypto broker and convert all the funds.
I installed the app too.
We can see that the price is going up way more slowly for a buyer
than for someone who isn't.
Wait, that's not right.
If they want to scam people, the price should surge for buyers.
A slow rise makes you buy more.
Otherwise, who would do that?
Everyone would want to cash out.
You see, for an average person like you,
earning less hurts the most.
Greedy guts.
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall, got too greedy, and had a great fall.
Well, this only proves that Tolita runs scams.
There's still no connection to William.
Dolly isn't just a spokesperson or figurehead.
She is essentially running the company.
We need to lure William out.
Then we need an even easier mark.
Don't look at me. I'm five million dollars in debt.
Thirty million.
Holy crap.
HUNG KUO-LUNG'S INVESTMENT PHILOSOPHY, RESUME
Next, we need to make Dolly believe
that you're an easy mark through Hung Kuo-lung.
Mr. Hung, I'm curious.
You are an investment adviser. Why become a broker?
Speaking of this makes me sad.
Two weeks ago, my mother passed away.
I really…
I really can't go on managing client accounts.
MEMBER INFORMATION
But I don't want to let them down.
How much of a cut do you want?
15%.
What you're asking is a first for me.
I need to think about it.
10%?
It's not the percentage. But thank you for the suggestion.
DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES
I feel like she sensed something was wrong.
She must think I was lying to her. I could see it in her eyes.
We want her to think you were lying to her.
Better yet, she finds out you run investment scams.
Fat sheep selected by a wolf are like goods in a curated store.
It's all handpicked.
How could another wolf resist making a move?
You three hustlers found a swindler to cheat a big scammer together.
I'm impressed.
Here, fat sheep. May you get rich.
GREEN DRAGON
I won.
South Wind, Four Seasons, dealer, and single wait. Four points.
Still hoping to win? You're getting fleeced.
You little…
Hello?
Hello? Is this Mr. Chiang Ming-shun?
You got the wrong number.
Hey.
Aren't you Mr. Chiang Ming-shun?
I am. Sorry, the signal wasn't great.
Hello, I'm calling from Tolita.
I am the CEO, Dolly.
I know.
My investment adviser, Hung Kuo-lung, said he wanted to help me invest in Dolly Bit.
But why did you contact me directly?
Well, you're one of our biggest investors.
We would like to invite you to our private investor dinner.
Oh, there's no need.
I'm interested in your product,
but I prefer not to spend time socializing.
How about this?
If there's anything, ask your boss to reach out directly.
I'll send you the address.
Um, sorry.
I'm boarding my flight.
-Keep in touch. -Mr. Chiang, let me…
Hello?
Are you flying out?
No.
Did you see a doctor?
My stomach has been bothering me. I keep having diarrhea.
You hate taking medicine. You wouldn't see a doctor for a cold.
What is that for?
The doctor said I must take something for the diarrhea.
Oh, so you won't tell me.
Mom! Mom, Dad--
Okay.
I'll tell you,
but you can't tell your mom.
Okay.
Did you see it?
Actually,
it keeps shaking.
Look.
Why is this happening?
Here, not here.
I know. I'm looking over there.
Have you heard of Parkinson's disease?
Sir Hong,
every day, many people come to pray to God.
Just how many people will receive his help?
God helps those who help themselves.
Those who come here
believe that holding a stick of incense
and chanting a few words will solve their problems.
You've been at Ching He Temple for many years,
but you don't believe in gods.
That's quite interesting.
I merely don't believe gods would help people like that.
One has to do their best
before letting God do the rest.
Besides Fixer Terra,
who do you think will be on our side?
It doesn't really matter whose side they will be on.
But
if Tristan Hsueh becomes mayor,
that will be a huge problem.
The Hsuehs are a prominent political family.
They have a strong network
and financial resources at their disposal.
Their reach even extends into law enforcement.
If Yeh Yueh Tong and the Hsueh family join forces and grow stronger,
you will have to face your fate.
But I still have a pawn that can keep the Hsueh family in check.
A single pawn cannot decide the outcome of the game.
Besides, it is uncertain if this pawn will turn out to be black or white.
There was only one pawn,
but God sent another one.
You sent them to find Gerald.
Will that work?
I have made every effort.
Now it's up to God.
Hey, buddy.
You don't think my reply to Dolly was too harsh?
Hey, it will be bad if she gets upset, and we don't hear back.
You've been around for a while. Haven't you heard of playing hard to get?
That's how I know people will actually walk away if you play too hard to get.
Hey, are you playing hard to get with Mina?
Listen, don't drag this out too long.
-When my wife and I-- -Are you done?
-I am. -Then come out already!
How do I look?
Like a fat sheep?
Like an old man at a wedding banquet.
Why do you insist on this tie?
It looks good. It's the first tie my wife ever gave me.
And your hairstyle.
It looks like it's from 50 years ago.
I've had a perm for 50 years. What do you mean?
Your belly.
It's entirely your issue.
Try another outfit.
Buddy, this is already the tenth.
Never mind, I'll take you somewhere. You'll be satisfied. One sec.
Ya.
Where's Hsien? Is he off today?
Felix! It has been a long time!
Yeah.
Dad passed away over three years ago.
Really?
Your son's suit looks very nice.
-Him? He's too old to be my son. -Yeah.
My son is in junior high right now.
So, Hsien… How did it happen?
He had a sudden stroke and passed away two or three years later.
Is that so?
I haven't been here in a decade.
I am Felix's colleague. I'm here to help him pick a suit.
Oh, sure. No problem.
Let's do it.
Felix, where do you work now?
I take gigs, I suppose.
182, 96.5, 86.4, 96.5.
He touched me all over.
You were measured eight times.
Time really flies.
I remember when we were younger,
you and Chi would come with liquor.
You guys wouldn't let me drink.
Here, try this.
Who told you to turn Chi down?
A decade went by in a flash. Your dad is gone.
Chi is gone too.
That row was made for the crew back then.
That's why it's designed that way.
This one really suits Felix.
He used to hate wearing that style.
He had my dad customize everything for him.
Custom-made is the way to go, okay?
He keeps saying he used to be part of the crew and had great aim.
Many feared him. Is that true?
Felix and Chi were known as
the Black and White Impermanence of the underworld.
One was a stone-faced sharpshooter, the other an intimidating fighter.
Stone-faced?
Yes, he gave himself the name.
Why is he such a smooth talker now?
How else can you survive in the world?
Hey.
You two, don't bad-mouth me while I'm changing, okay?
If nothing had happened to Chi back then,
maybe they'd still be prowling the streets.
Hey.
Take a look.
Is it okay?
Gosh. So handsome.
-Let me see. -Finally.
Let me check the waistline.
No need to alter it. It fits.
-And the pant length? -It's okay. I have a model's build.
You left your clothes.
I don't want them anymore.
Good riddance.
THE GENTLEMEN'S SUIT SHOP, PREMIUM SUITS
Mr. Chiang.
Have a seat.
Is he the boss?
He is our crypto broker.
I'm the person in charge, Dolly.
So no one else is above? It's just you?
Yes, I am the person in charge.
You're so young.
Come on, let's eat.
Do you find it strange that I chose to meet you here?
Why would we? Who says you need fancy rooms for investment talks?
True.
This stir-fry eatery is where my business started.
Twenty years ago, I sat in this very spot.
I was so poor
that I could only order swamp eel noodles without swamp eel.
Do you know what I overheard the next table talking about?
Venturing abroad.
Hung Kuo-lung runs stock scams. It's best to steer clear of him.
I know. So I went around him and contacted the Taiwanese businessman in Dubai.
Something about his information seems fishy.
Find out what his intentions are. Don't rush into committing. Okay?
Got it.
What about me? When are you going to let me take over Yuan Tao?
It's tiring to keep lying.
I don't trust anyone else with Tolita.
Mr. Chiang, I'm curious.
What does your company do in Dubai?
I develop medical technologies.
I did a quick check.
How come I don't see the company generating any cash flow or output?
Listen. The tech company is just a front.
My real business is… in games of chance.
Got it?
No wonder.
I want to get into investing too.
I don't want others to say that I'm a gambler who relies on luck, yeah?
Excuse me, Mr. Chiang.
We carefully vet each investor at Tolita.
Because, you know, it's fairer and safer for all investors.
You don't believe me?
I'll just be frank.
I know some Taiwanese businessmen in Dubai.
But no one has heard of you.
Take a look.
I know you all like cash, right?
You won't botch it, right?
Mr. Chiang, don't worry.
Okay, come on.
The taste hasn't changed at all in 20 years.
That man couldn't stand my words and took out his money.
That influencer was worried I had no money and tried to bait me.
The cash instantly changed her tune.
She immediately took it, signed, and showed me the app.
Take care of the cash first. I'll see you later.
She's probably taking the cash directly to a money launderer.
We're following her car.
Okay. Hey.
You two wanna come over for a bite after?
I ordered way too much.
If you do come, I'll leave and let you two eat alone, okay?
Why act like strangers? We're so close already, aren't we?
Fine, I'll eat it myself.
Here.
How did you know I only eat these two things?
I didn't.
I just happen to not eat those two.
The money launderer is here.
Why not just buy gold bars on the black market?
The launderer will turn the cash into globally accepted crypto
and transfer it to Dolly's overseas account.
Handling it this way is more discreet.
But meeting a launderer doesn't link Tolita to William.
How much have you made according to the app?
Around 4%. Just like you said, it's rising slowly.
Time for another fat sheep to appear with the old one.
My previous investment is showing profits on paper.
I'm not in a hurry to sell.
Let the profits continue to grow.
You're a real big shot.
You know that long-term holding can pay off big.
But why don't you consider adding to your position?
You can rake in more profits.
That's what I thought too.
But I found another investment product.
This company helped me earn 40% in less than a month.
40%?
How is that possible? Are you sure?
There isn't that much bullish news in the market right now.
Look, this is their invitation.
I looked into it. It's a Singaporean company.
But apart from this, there is no other information.
It might be a scam company.
Check it out.
There will be many investors. It's not a bad thing to poach a few.
This is your final task.
Invite your investment clients to our cocktail party.
That's easy.
But will this really lure William out?
Just wait and see.
However, this stack…
Thanks for taking care of me.
Hey, this is the CEO.
She might be young, but she knows finance better than her father.
I'll be counting on you.
Just call me Mandy.
Okay, let's keep in touch.
-Okay. -Sure.
Keep in touch.
Sure, keep in touch.
-See you. -Okay, bye.
Hello, I am the CEO of Tolita.
Call me Dolly.
Tolita?
Hello.
By the way, that snack you told me about tastes really good.
-Really? -Mandy.
Just wanted to say hello.
The younger son of the Hsuehs, Louis.
-Hello. -Hello.
You're like your brother, a fine fellow.
No, my brother is ambitious. I prefer money.
-How long have you been a member? -Just over a month. I've made a bit.
-There will be many more opportunities. -Of course.
I'll let you chat. I have to go welcome a director.
I'll tell you about some derivatives later.
I'll be waiting for you.
Your suit looks great.
It took me a while to decide.
Excuse me. Mind lending me a cigarette?
The pack is done.
You're here to poach clients, aren't you?
Sorry, I don't quite understand.
Trading crypto. I know about your company.
You're quite convincing too.
Every client inside has a nine-figure net worth.
You expect me to hand you a win?
You stole one of my investors, so I came to take a look.
I didn't steal him.
He was drawn in.
For a company this young, you have major clients.
You must have a backer, right?
We are a proper business.
If you want to know,
I'm happy to tell you.
We actually collaborate with Yuan Tao.
Their cofounder, William, is one of our shareholders.
If you join us,
we can share the profits.
Of course there will be conditions.
I really thought you were legit.
So you're a scammer.
What makes you say that?
You can't possibly be working with Yuan Tao.
Do you know William?
So you are the one who works with Yuan Tao after all.
I was going to say, Tolita has impressive scale for being so young.
But doesn't Yuan Tao know Tolita runs financial scams?
Where did you hear these rumors?
Don't you know launderers gossip a lot?
But don't worry. I won't run my mouth.
I just want to make money.
How about this?
Since I've attracted these major clients,
why don't we meet with William?
Let's turn a lie into reality and make money together.
If William doesn't know your company runs scams,
I'll keep it a secret for you.
If he knows, I'll do it for both of you.
When I profit from collaborating with Yuan Tao,
I'll give you a cut.
What do you think?
The Hsuehs' younger son was there too?
Yes.
He even said he made a lot of money from investing with that company.
If Mandy knows those launderers, she can't be anyone good.
She can't be scamming Louis, can she?
After all, his family is powerful.
They must be targeting easy marks.
She claims to be collaborating with me.
I can't just leave her be.
So you wanna meet her?
One less enemy can't hurt.
And there are indeed many easy targets.
Okay, let me confirm one thing.
We recommend long-term investments.
We believe in the value of blockchain technology.
It isn't just for short-term speculation.
So, of course, Yuan Tao will continue to focus on this area.
BARRAGE OF BEARISH NEWS TRIGGERS CRYPTO BLOODBATH!
At this age,
I'm no longer used to catching a breeze in the evening
up at a place like this.
I only drink tea now.
Long time no see.
Pardon the liquor.
My father used to tell me
that of all the branches, he admired you the most.
You are the calmest and shrewdest.
Gosh, let's skip the pleasantries.
What do you want to discuss?
I know you and Thackery are old friends.
That bond is hard to sever.
I just want to remind you
that sometimes, not taking a stance
is a stance in itself.
What if
I choose to take a stance?
All I know is if you don't take a stance,
those rumors will disappear,
and your position will be secure.
And all I know is that
choosing Thackery to take over as Fixer Celestial back then
was the right choice.
But now,
insisting that he stay isn't necessarily a good idea.
Don't forget Ching He's principle.
Turn big problems into small ones
and small problems into nothing.
I'm too old to be out in the wind.
It's a pity I can't enjoy this fine liquor.
I heard you've made quite a bit recently investing with Hsin Yueh.
Aren't you a shareholder?
Mandy told me that only after I invested.
You hid that well.
I really should learn from you.
You already have financial freedom,
but it looks like you're not retiring.
It's like a ball game.
Winning money from someone else
feels like winning a competition.
Most of all, you feel accomplished.
I'm beginning to get it.
Okay. See you at the restaurant.
How was it?
William wants to see me.
Finally.
How will you make him disclose his connection to Tolita?
He now believes I run scams too.
If he wants to collaborate,
Tolita will have to come in.
If he doesn't,
he'll ask you not to reveal that Tolita runs scams.
Either way, it will prove that he is connected to the company, right?
It's such a waste for you to be a fixer.
If only I had met you sooner, damn!
My gambling den would've been fine.
You're awesome.
Felix said you're meeting with William tomorrow.
Tomorrow night.
What's on your mind?
I've been investigating all this time.
If the result isn't what I want,
what do I do?
Ben gave you this.
No radishes or pork meatballs.
Do you know he never offers it
unless I order from him?
Just eat.
Why did you want to be a fixer?
If my brother ever runs into a problem he can't handle, I can help.
It'll also remind my dad that he has two sons.
It'll go smoothly tomorrow.
You've improved.
Ten to seven.
Gosh, you're off your game today.
Gotta let you earn a bit sometimes, or I'll have nowhere to play if you move.
Thank you.
-This is for you. -Oh, thank you.
A gun for you.
-Practice more. -I've never gotten this.
-Thank you. Bye. -Come on, I'll treat you.
Haven't been here in a while, and it's up another ten.
Prices these days.
What's wrong? Does it not taste good anymore?
Today was your first loss to me.
That's how it's supposed to be.
I will grow old, and you will grow up.
Why won't you tell Mom you're sick?
Telling her now will only make her worry more.
I looked it up online.
Do you know your condition will only get worse?
Of course I do.
So one day,
you'll have to take care of your mom, got it?
What are you talking about? Are you underestimating me?
I can take care of you too, okay?
Also, Mom isn't as weak as you make her out to be.
Do I need you to tell me that?
When she's fuming, I can forget about going home.
You'd better start thinking about her birthday gift.
Like I don't know. I've got an idea.
It will definitely satisfy the empress.
Come on, eat. Her favorite stinky tofu shop is closing.
Then hurry up and buy it.
Your chicken cutlet isn't coming that soon.
Good idea.
You can have the teppanyaki noodles, but my chicken cutlet… is off-limits.
Do you hear me?
CHIA-YUN
I've booked the plane ticket. Counting down till I leave.
Don't miss me too much.
Yes.
Yes, okay.
Okay, good.
Fuck, what is this?
It will be handled per party policy. Politics plays no part in this.
We cannot waver in our principles due to political winds,
nor can we let a single incident
dampen our determination for reform.
My father is in good health.
He remains committed to society and its people. Thank you every…
Breaking news…
Don't wait. He's not coming.
From what is known so far, rescue workers found the body in the mountains.
Cause of death and motive remain unclear.
This tragic news shocked more than just the business sector.
Yuan Tao's successor and stock outlook…
YUAN TAO COFOUNDER REPORTEDLY COMMITTED SUICIDE IN THE MOUNTAINS
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu